Wolf, Benjamin Additional Arbitration Files 5803
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Benjamin Wolf Additional Arbitration Files
1982-1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wolf, Benjamin
5803
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Includes arbitration awards, decisions, and related documents for cases arbitrated in the transportation, chemicals, clothing, retail food and retail trade, manufacturing, publishing, health care, bakery and confectionery, television, coal and oil, construction and electronics industries. Also, arbitration for various education and civil service agencies, primarily of the state of New York and New York City.
5710638
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 30, 1988
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, June 27, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Arbitrator, labor mediator and attorney; visiting professor, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University. Wolf served as permanent arbitrator between the New York City Board of Education and the United Federation of Teachers; New York City and the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME); the New York City Off-Track Betting Corp. and AFSCME; New York State and AFSCME; the State University of New York and the Senate Professional Association; A. Goodman and the American Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Union; and between the Simmons Company and the Upholsterers International Union. Wolf also served as impartial chairman for American Airlines and the Transport Workers Union of America; the men's shirt industry and the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; and the Brooklyn Union Gas Company and the Transport Workers Union of America.
Born May 6, 1909. Attended Cornell University (B.A. 1930; LL.B. 1932).
Formerly labor mediator, New York State Board of Meidation; labor relations examiner, N.Y.S. Labor Relations Board.
Affiliated with National Academy of Arbitrators (board of governors 1971-; regional chairman 1967-1968); Industrial Relations Research Association; Society for Professionals in Dispute Resolution; New York Bar Association. On rosters of American Arbitration Association, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, National Mediation Board, New York State Board of Mediation, New Jersey State Board of Mediation, New York Public Employment Relations Board, New Jersey Public Employment Relations Commission.
Arbitrator under contract for N.Y. City Board of Education and UFT; City of New York and District Council 37; OTB and DC37; N.Y. State and Council 82, AFSCME: State University of New York and Senate Professional Association; Metropolitan New York Milk Industry and IBT; New Rochelle Board of Education and UFT; A. Goodman & Sons and BCWU; Metropolitan Association of Optical Wholesalers and IUE; Simons Co. and Local 420, UIU.
Impartial Chairman; American Airlines and TWU, Men's Shirt Industry and ACWA; Brooklyn Union Gas and TWU; Williams Press and Pressmen's Union; Hiring Hall & Club Employees Union (Local 16); Westchester County Laundry Board of Trade and Local 335 IBT: Rochdale Village, Inc. and Local 90 Public Service Union; Ossining Board of Education and Ossining Teachers Association; Schwartz Laboratories, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers; Ross Oil Term. Corp., Howard Fuel Corp. & Local 365 UAW.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5305: Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5477: Benjamin Wolf Papers 5511: Benjamin Wolf Additional Papers 5539: Benjamin H. Wolf Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State); Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Industrial relations -- New York (State); Industrial relations -- United States; Employee-management relations in government -- New York (State); Wolf, Benjamin H., b.1909
5710638
- 82-21 Levin Fixture Corporation vs. Local 2682, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (U.B. of C.&J of A.), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  RC. Cancelled.
- 82-22 New York State vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, Council 82, Attica, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  RC. Withdrawn.
- 82-23 New York State, Department of Vocational Rehabilitation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  RC. Settled.
- 82-24 New York State Office of Mental Retardation, Staten Island Developmental Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  2 Cases: 1)Issue: Fights and Altercations--Provocation; 2)Issue: Insubordination--Failure To Obey Orders. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- 82-25 New York State (D. D. Heck) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) (Ralph Wade, et al), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 82-26 New York State Unified Court System vs. Court Officers' Benevolent Association of Nassau County, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  AN, LD, RC. Award upheld.
- 82-27 New York City vs. Communications Workers of America, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Past Practice. EX, LD, AN, RC, A.
- 82-28 New York State, Letchworth Village Departmental Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Penalties. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-30 KSM Division, Omark Industries vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Issue: Discipline-- Discharge. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-31 E.I. DuPont De Nemours and Company vs. Local 11, Federation of Independent Unions, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Issue: Posting--Removal of Notice. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-32 United States Post Office vs. National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Issue: Absences--Notice in General. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-33 New York State vs. Brooklyn DC, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  RC. Taken to different arbitrator.
- 82-34 Crescent News vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverer's Union, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 82-35 New Jersey State vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 82-36 New Jersey State vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Issue: Reduction in Force--Assignment of Jobs. TR, EX, LD, AN, RC, A, SD.
- 82-36 New Jersey State vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 82-37 New York State, Suffolk Developmental Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Assaults. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-38 Friars Club vs. Local 6, Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees and Bartenders Union, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 82-39 City of Yonkers, New York vs. Uniformed Fire Officers Association, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  RC, A. Withdrawn.
- 82-40 New York State, Bronx Psychiatric Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Assault. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-41 Peekskill City School District vs. Peekskill Faculty Association, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  2 Cases, Issues: 1) Schedules of Work--Change of Schedule. 2) Arbitrability--Scope of Issue. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- 82-42 State of New York, Office of Mental Retardation, Wassaic Developmental Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Assaults; Negligence. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-43 New York City vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 768, District Council 37, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 82-44 United Parcel Service vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 177, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- 82-45 Wilson Jones Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 102, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-46 The River Club of New York, Inc. vs. Local 6, Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees and Bartenders Union, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-46 The River Club of New York, Inc. vs. Local 6, Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees and Bartenders Union, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- 82-47 GAF Corporation vs. Local 146, General Industrial Workers Union, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Elimination of Jobs. TR, EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- 82-47 GAF Corporation vs. Local 146, General Industrial Workers Union, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- 82-48 New York State, Office of Employee Relations (OER) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- 82-49 New York City vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 82-50 New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive, Discipline. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-51 Pearl River School District vs. Pearl River Teachers' Association, New York State United Teachers, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 82-52 New York State, Office of Mental Retardation, Bernard Fineson Developmental Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 82-53 New York State, Letchworth Village Developmental Center vs. Leo Greston, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Issue: Absences--Falsification of Report; Improper Job Attitude--Neglect of Duty. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- 82-53 New York State, Letchworth Village Developmental Center vs. Leo Greston, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 82-54 Standard Keil Hardware Manufacturing Company vs. Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Issue: Absences--Discipline. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-55 Home News Publishing Company vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Issue: Vacation Pay--Eligibility. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-56 New York City, Board of Elections vs. Communications Workers of America, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Issue: Back Pay Awards--Grievance and Grievance Procedure. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-57 Elizabethtown Gas Company vs. Utility Workers of America, Local 424, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  RC. Cancelled(?).
- 82-58 GAF Corporation vs. General Industrial Workers Union, Local 146, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge. Grievance Dismissed. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-59 United Hospitals Medical Center vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), District 1199J, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 82-60 Bamberger's (Bloomfield) vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 177, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline--Suspensions; Supervisors and Foremen. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-61 New York State, Office of Employee Relations vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 82-62 New York State, Office of Mental Health, Manhattan Psychiatric Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-63 New York City vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 420, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Issue: Insubordination--Discipline; Fights and Altercations--Assault on Supervisor. EX, AN, RC.
- 82-64 DeDietrich (USA), Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW), District 15, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Issue: Theft--Unauthorized Taking of Property. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 82-65 United States Postal Service vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 82-66 New York State, Suffolk Developmental Center vs. Public Employees Federation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  RC. Unable to schedule second hearing, taken to different arbitrator.
- 82-67 United States Postal Service vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 83-1 E.I. Dupont deNemours and Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union (ICWU), Local 527, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Inability. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-2 State of New Jersey vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  RC. (a scheduling letter).
- 83-3 New York State vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 83-4 Eastern Delivery Service vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 177, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 83-5 Spetonbush/Red Star Companies vs. International Longshoremen's Association (ILA), Local 133, United Marine Division, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- 83-6 United States Postal Service (UPS) vs. National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 83-7 State of New Jersey (William Patterson College) vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Issue: Premium Pay-- Weather Conditions; Absences--Unauthorized. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-8 State of New Jersey, Department of Transportation vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- 83-9 State of New Jersey, Department of Law and Public Safety vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Issue: Layoff-- Recall. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-10 New York State vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- 83-11 Onteora Central School District vs. Onteora Teachers' Association, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure-- Timeliness; Assignment of Jobs--Assignment of Work Outside Unit. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-12 New York State vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- 83-13 National Gypsum Company (Gold Bond Building Products) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union 5476, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Issue: Absences--Discipline. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-14 Amerace Corporation, Esna Division vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 726, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Issue: Contracting Out--Bargaining Unit Work. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-15 Family Services Association of Middlesex County vs. District 1199J, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Issue: Fringe Benefits--Holiday Pay, Sick Leave and Sick Pay, Vacation Pay, Maternity Leave; Arbitrability--Subject Matter. EX, RC, A.
- 83-16 New York City, Office of Municipal Labor Relations, Department of Correction vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 832, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Assault on Fellow Employee. EX, AN, RC.
- 83-17 GAF Corporation vs. General Industrial Workers Union (GIWU), Local 146, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  2 Cases, Issues: 1) Schedules of Work--Change of Schedule, Premium Pay. 2) Assignment of Jobs--Change in Procedure. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-18 State of New Jersey, Department of Transportation vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1031, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Issue: Overtime--Rates of Pay; Vacations--Scheduling. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-19 New York State, Letchworth Village vs. Richard Wolfe, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 83-20 Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local Union #2006, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 83-21 New Jersey Transit Bus Operations, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 880, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Issue: Discipline--Drinking. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-22 Sherwin-Williams Company vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), Local 8-917, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Combination of Classifications. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-23 Blue Cross/Blue Shield of New Jersey vs. Office and Professional Employees International Union, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Issue: Standards of Production--Failure to Meet. AN, RC, A.
- 83-24 Spatenbush/Red Star Company vs. Local 333, United Marine Division, International Longshoremen's Association (ILA), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Issue: Seniority--Recall. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-25 The City of New York, Department of Correction vs. Corrective Officers' Benevolent Association (COBA), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Issue: Overtime-- Refusal of Overtime. EX, AN, RC.
- 83-26 Family Service Association of Middlesex County vs. District 1199-J, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- 83-27 Alcan, Ingot, and Powders, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union #12243, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Issue: Posting--Bidding Qualifications.
- 83-28 Saint Joseph's Hospital vs. Communication Workers of America (CWA), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay--Part-Time Employees. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-29 New York State, Office of Employee Relations vs. Roger I. Paulmeno, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- 83-30 Bendix Corporation, Electric Power Division, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Temporary Assignment. AN, RC, A.
- 83-31 State of New York, Unified Court System vs. Suffolk County Court Employees Association, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- 83-32 Delman Shoe Salon and I. Miller Company vs. Retail Shoe Employees Union, Local 237, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Time Not Worked. EX, AN, RC.
- 83-33 Mineola Union Free School District (UFSD) vs. Mineola Teachers' Association, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Issue: Plant Rules--Record-Keeping. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-34 M.S. and W. Distributors, Inc. d/b/a Suffern Tri-County Distributors, Inc. vs. Local 56, Brewery Workers and Delivery Employees, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Issue: Sale of Business--Retention of Rights. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-35 Hutchings Psychiatric Center vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 83-36 New York Times vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 83-37 New York City, Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. Correction Officers' Benevolent Association (COBA), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 83-38 New York State vs. Safety Officers, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 83-39 Continental Corrugated, A Member of the Continental Group, Inc. vs. United Paperworkers International Union (UPIU), Local 1275, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Vacancies. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 83-40 New York City vs. Local 621, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Holiday Pay. EX, AN, RC.
- 83-41 Transamerica Delaval, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 661, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 83-42 The Association of Catholic Schools For Sacred Heart School vs. Federation of Catholic Teachers, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 83-43 American Bank Note Company vs. Local 119B-43B Graphic Arts, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Issue: Transfers--Transfers of Work and Machines. EX, LD, AN, RC, A.
- 83-44 New York City Off-Track Betting Corporation vs. Local 2021, District Council 37, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Issue: Physical Disability--Recall. EX, AN, RC.
- 83-45 GAF Corporation vs. General Industrial Workers Union (GIWU), Local 146, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Faulty Production. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- 83-46 Ozone Industries, Inc. vs. District 15, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 83-47 United States Postal Service vs. American Postal Workers Union (APWU), Newark, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Issue: Absences--Unauthorized. EX, AN, RC.
- 83-48 New Jersey State vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1040, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 83-49 Tenney Engineering, Inc. vs. Sheet Metal Workers, Local 172, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- 83-50 New York Times vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- 83-51 New York State Unified Court System vs. Court Officers' Benevolent Association, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- 83-52 St. Mary Hospital vs. District 1199J, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- 83-53 Anheuser Busch, Inc. vs. Local 102, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 83-54 Acme Engraving Company vs. Dyers and Finishers, Local 1932, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- 83-55 Perth Amboy Dry Dock Company vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- 83-56 St. Mary's Hospital vs. Service Employees' International Union (SEIU), Local 144, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Issue: Theft--Failure To Report Theft; Theft--Penalty. EX, AN, RC.
- 83-57 Rochester Telephone Corporation vs. Rochester Telephone Workers Union, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- 84-1 New York State Court Administration vs. Suffolk County Court Clerks Association, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- 84-2 Sperry Division, Sperry Corporation vs. Engineers Union, Local 444; International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers (IUE), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Timeliness; Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Failure To Follow; Promotions--Refusal. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-3 Finch, Pruyn and Company, Inc. vs. United Paperworkers' International Union, Local 18, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations-- Threats; Insubordination--Profanity. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-4 New York City, Office of Municipal and Labor Relations (NYC OMLR) vs. Correction Officers Benevolent Association (COBA), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 28a)
  Issue: Vacations--Eligibility. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- 84-5 Sperry Corporation vs. Engineers' Union, Local 444, International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers (IUE), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Issue: Fringe Benefits--Insurance and Medical Plans. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-5 Sperry Corporation vs. Engineers' Union, Local 444, International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers (IUE), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- 84-6 Simmons U.S.A. vs. Upholsterers' International Union, Local 420, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Issue: Insubordination--Refusal of Work Assignment. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-7 Sperry Corporation vs. Engineers' Union, Local 444, International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers (IUE), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- 84-8 GAF Corporation vs. General Industrial Workers Union, Local 146, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Issue: Supervisors and Foremen--Discipline by Union. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- 84-9 U.S. Government Immigration and Naturalization Service vs. American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), Local 1917, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Timeliness; Vacations--Eligibility, Scheduling. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-10 Concord Hotel vs. Hotel Workers, Local 76, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Issue: Theft--Suspicion, Discipline. AN, RC.
- 84-11 U.S. Postal Service vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 84-12 St. Joseph's Hospital vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1040, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Timeliness; Insubordination--Refusal of Work Assignment. EX, AN, RC, A.
- 84-13 ITT Continental Baking vs. Bakery Drivers and Salesman, Local 194, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 84-14 U.S. Postal Service vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 84-16 GAF Corporation vs. General Industrial Workers' Union, Local 146, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)